[
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515a2",
    "correctAnswer": "Three ",
    "answers": ["Two", "Three ", "Four", "Five"],
    "question": "How many pieces of bun are in a Mcdonald's Big Mac?",
    "tags": ["food", "food_and_drink"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e2d",
    "correctAnswer": "L. Frank Baum",
    "answers": [
      "Suzanne Collins",
      "James Fenimore Cooper",
      "L. Frank Baum",
      "Donna Leon"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'The Wonderful Wizard of Oz'?",
    "tags": ["literature", "arts_and_literature"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport & Leisure",
    "id": "62417cc18c3137686862d737",
    "correctAnswer": "Atlanta United",
    "answers": [
      "Atlanta United",
      "Atlanta Impact",
      "Atlanta Bulls",
      "Atlanta Stars"
    ],
    "question": "Which of these is a soccer team based in Atlanta?",
    "tags": ["sport"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "62433421cfaae40c12961425",
    "correctAnswer": "A Nanny",
    "answers": ["A Sow", "A Lioness", "A Hen", "A Nanny"],
    "question": "A female goat is known as what?",
    "tags": ["science"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950de1",
    "correctAnswer": "P. L. Travers",
    "answers": [
      "J. R. R. Tolkien",
      "P. L. Travers",
      "Lewis Carroll",
      "Enid Blyton"
    ],
    "question": "Which author wrote 'Mary Poppins'?",
    "tags": ["literature", "childrens_literature", "arts_and_literature"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb48",
    "correctAnswer": "Terms of Endearment",
    "answers": [
      "Terms of Endearment",
      "The Big Chill",
      "The Dresser",
      "The Right Stuff"
    ],
    "question": "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1983?",
    "tags": ["academy_awards", "film", "film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506ce",
    "correctAnswer": "Jon Favreau",
    "answers": [
      "Seth Rogen",
      "John Turturro",
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme",
      "Jon Favreau"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including My Name Is Earl and Spider-Man: Homecoming?",
    "tags": ["film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62602d9d4b176d54800e3ca5",
    "correctAnswer": "Hungary",
    "answers": ["Luxembourg", "Hungary", "Moldova", "Greece"],
    "question": "In which country is the city of Budapest?",
    "tags": ["cities", "europe", "geography"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950da7",
    "correctAnswer": "ABBA",
    "answers": ["In Flames", "HammerFall", "ABBA", "Katatonia"],
    "question": "Which band includes 'Agnetha FÃ¤ltskog'?",
    "tags": ["music"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950617",
    "correctAnswer": "Zoe Saldana",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine Deneuve",
      "Audrey Hepburn",
      "Rachel Weisz",
      "Zoe Saldana"
    ],
    "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Guardians of the Galaxy and Avatar?",
    "tags": ["film_and_tv"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": false
  }
]
